我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at s.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
我让杀害母亲的凶手自食其果
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
but in doing so, I opened up our world to new threats,
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I am the only one fast enough to stop them.
我叫闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
现在震波全面开启
I'm in full-on vibe mode right now.
但我不够快  没能保护爱瑞丝
I wasn't fast enough to protect Iris.
我感觉自己慢了
I felt slower.
是我干的  我偷走了你的速度
I did it. I stole your speed.
把它给了极速
I gave it to Zoom.
把我女儿还给我
Give me back my daughter.
我要闪电侠其余的速度
Bring me the rest of Flash's speed.
我说过我们是一个团队
I told you we're a team.
我们要帮你救出杰西
We're gonna help you save Jesse.
我们一起去地球二
We're going to Earth-2.
日志记录  115条
Journal log entry 115,
我的最后一条
My last entry.
在这个地球上  我们正在关闭缺口
On this earth, we're closing the breaches,
所有的缺口
all of them.
很快  所有连接两个地球的通道
Soon, every portal between this earth and mine
都会消失
will no longer exist.
我被这地球吸引住了
I've become distracted by this earth,
这里的难题  这里的人
its problems, its people.
二十九
29.
二十八
28.
二十七
27.
二十六
26.
但是我唯一没有忘记的
But the one thing I never lost track of
就是你  杰西
was you, Jesse.
你是我的良心  我跳动的心脏
You are my conscience, my beating heart.
为了你我与极速
You're the reason I made it this far
长期抗争  而现在
in my fight against Zoom, and now
我只需要你撑住
I just need you to hang on.
再撑一下子  因为...
Hang on a little bit longer because...
我就要去救你了
I'm coming to get you,
而这一次
And this time...
我不是一个人
I'm not coming alone.
缺口状态  关闭
这就搞定了
That's how it's done.
他射门得分了
He shoots. He scores.
体育中下水平的人的超常表现
Not bad for a guy who got a C in gym.
我刚过及格线
D plus.
我直接就不及格
Straight up F right here.
真不敢相信  我们关闭了所有缺口
Can't believe it. We closed all the breaches.
只剩下一个
All except the one.
尖端科研实验室
缺口状态  活跃
我们去地球二的最后通道
Our last way to Earth-2.
准备好了吗
Ready?
好了  我就差最后几件事要先处理下
Yeah, I just have a few things to take care of first.
提醒你一下  艾伦
Just a reminder, Allen...
时间不等人
Clock's ticking.
什么时候不是
It always is.
自从我大学毕业后你就没做过千层面了
You know you haven't made lasagna since I left for college?
上大学比去另一个地球近多了
College is a hell of a lot closer than another earth.
你告诉亨利了吗
Did you tell Henry?
没有  如果他知道了
No. I--look, if he knew,
他只会试着劝我放弃
He would just try to talk me out of it
而且他没准会成功  所以...
and he probably would, so...
爸爸  能让我们单独聊聊吗
Dad, can you give us a minute?
好  我去给咱泡点咖啡
Yeah, I'll make us some coffee.
爱瑞丝
Look, Iris.
我知道这事很...
I know that this is...
我只能用"疯狂"来形容
nuts is the only word I can think of right now,
可我以前也做过
but it's not like I've never done
很多危险的事
anything dangerous before.
我知道你为什么要这么做
Look, I--I get why you are doing this.
无辜的人身处险境
Innocent people are in danger.
而那种地方总是你奔跑的方向
That's always been the direction that you've run in,
即便是你跑得慢的时候
even--even when you ran a little bit slower.
我只是
I just...
想知道
I want to make sure
你做这件事  不是因为你觉得
that you're not doing this because you think
你在这里已经没有牵挂了
that you don't have anything left here anymore.
不是因为帕蒂
This isn't about Patty.
不是
It's not.
我是说  当然了  我很想她
I mean, of course, you know, I miss her a lot,
但我知道我在这里拥有什么
but I know what I have here.
我爱我的生活
I love my life.
我爱我的工作  爱当闪电侠
I love my job, being the Flash.
我爱你和乔
I love you and Joe.
我不是想逃跑
I'm not trying to escape.
我保证
I promise.
去打场胜战  巴里
Go win, Barry,
然后回家来
and then come home.
好的
All right.
好了  巴里  听我说
All right, Barry, listen to me.
你将要通过镜子屋
You're about to go through the looking glass.
你将看到很多相似的东西
You're gonna see things that look and feel familiar,
但它们却不一样
but they're not.
上变下  黑变白
Up is down. Black is white,
别让你自己被困在情感之中
And do not let yourself get sucked in emotionally,
祝你好运
and good luck.
如果我们48小时之内没回来
Look, if we're not back in 48 hours,
表示我们败给极速了
that means that Zoom has us.
如果真是如此
If that happens,
你们就得关闭缺口
you have to close the breach.
我们不会关的
We're not gonna do that.
你要安全回来  好吗
You get yourself back here in one piece, all right?
别让我去找你
Don't make me come and get you.
不会
No.
这是写给我父母和丹堤的
I wrote this for my parents and Dante.
我要是回不来  记得交给他
If I don't come back, make sure he gets them.
西斯科  你会回来的
Cisco, you're coming back.
凯特琳  求你了
Caitlin, please.
好  我会的
Okay, I will.
谢谢
Thank you.
-小心点  -好
- Be careful. - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
-你也小心点  哈里  -斯诺
- You too, Harry. - Snow.
希望能救回你女儿
I hope you get your daughter back.
我保证你儿子也会回来的
I'll make sure you get your son back.
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
不  有必要
Yeah, I do.
有人跟我一样害怕吗
Is anybody else feeling panic right now?
18岁的时候我都不敢蹦极
I chickened out of bungee jumping when I was 18,
但这绝对要吓人得多
but this is categorically a lot scarier.
一旦我打开神速炮
Once I turn the speed cannon on,
你们仨就可以安全通过
the three of you will be able to pass through unharmed,
可巴里你得保证你的速度能提上来
but Barry, you need to make sure you keep your speed up.
我喉咙发紧
I--I got no spit.
《大白鲨》
"Jaws."
我不只是在引用《大白鲨》的台词
I'm not just quoting "Jaws."
我是说现在嘴里真的很干
I mean my mouth is really dry right now.
别被路上见到的东西分了心
Do not get distracted by anything you see along the way.
我们会见到什么
What are we gonna see?
什么都可能
Everything.
开始吧  杰伊
Do it, Jay.
好  我们走
Okay, let's go.
凯特琳  小心
Caitlin, look out!
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事
Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
怎么了
What happened?
其余的缺口都关闭了
With the rest of the breaches closed,
能量集中到最后这个缺口
the energy surge to this last remaining breach
造成它不稳定
must have destabilized it.
什么意思
Well, what does that mean?
如果缺口无法稳定
As long as it's unstable
巴里和西斯科就无法回来
Barry and Cisco will be trapped over there.
妈呀2001年
Holy 2001.
感觉像是开了第三只眼
I feel like I just opened my third eye.
天呐
Oh, my god.
来吧
Come on.
欢迎来到地球二
Welcome to Earth-2.
兄弟  这里感觉完全不想堪萨斯州啊
Toto, I've got a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.
太神奇了
This is amazing.
这里一半的东西在地球一上都还是概念
Half these things are just ideas on our earth.
-过来  -我是说
- Come here. - I mean--
-拉蒙  -什么事
- Ramon. - What?
咱们不是来观光的
Not a sightseeing tour.
就你那么想
Speak for yourself.
我们还想让孙辈们看看咱们有多酷呢
We want our grandkids to know we did cool stuff.
-威尔斯博士  -亨利
- Dr. Wells. - Henry.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
什么风把你吹来了
We weren't expecting you.
是啊
Yes...
没人知道我回来了
I didn't tell anyone I was coming back.
发生了那么多事
I thought you might've left town
我以为你已经离开了呢
with all that's been happening.
-对  -你朋友没事吧
- Right. - Are your friends okay?
没事  他们没事
Yes, they're-- they're fine.
只是容易激动
They're excitable.
这位是
This is, um...
亨利·翰威特  实验室助理
Henry Hewitt, lab assistant.
很高兴认识你们
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
幸会  我是巴里
And you-- um, this is Barry.
这位是西斯科
This is Cisco.
-我叫西斯科  -对
- I'm Cisco. - Yeah.
而你是个正常的好人
And you are just a nice, normal guy.
好
Okay, um--
威尔斯博士  你和你朋友
Dr. Wells, will you and your visitors
需要用会议室吗
be needing the conference room?
不必了  亨利
Not necessary, Henry.
我们很快就走
Our visit will be short.
-好的  -很高兴见到你
- Okay. - Good to see you.
很高兴见到你  先生
Good to see you, sir.
他在地球一上是个坏蛋
He's a bad guy on Earth-1.
他们俩长得很像
He looks just like him.
温馨提示  全市范围实行宵禁
A reminder that a citywide curfew has been issued.
极速威胁依然存在
史纳特市长延长宵禁
未经批准任何人不得在晚上九点之后出门
No unauthorized person is to be out after 9:00 P.M.
近日极速袭击次数上升
A recent increase in Zoom attacks
史纳特市长延长了宵禁
has led Mayor Snart to extend the curfew.
全市发生一系列恐怖袭击之后
The curfew was first issued after a series
市长首次下达了宵禁令
of terror attacks throughout the city...
更严重了
It's worse.
比我离开的时候还要严重
It's worse than when I left.
极速在这座城市卷起了腥风血雨
Zoom has turned up his reign of terror.
好  那我们得尽快找到极速
All right, then let's find Zoom fast.
西斯科  干活儿
Cisco, do your thing.
好  极速
All right, Zoom...
你跑得快  可你躲不掉
you can run, but you can't hide.
好了  是这样的
All right, you know what?
你们俩在这里有点挤
You guys are crowding my space a little bit.
压力太大我无法发功  好吗
I can't perform like this under pressure, okay?
你们可不可以往后退一点
If you could just step back just a little bit,
-我得开始发功了  -好
- I need to do my thing. - All right.
-我的超能力  -好的
- My mojo. - Yes, all right.
谢谢
Thank you.
第二次尝试
Take two...
好了  极速
All right, Zoom.
你跑得快
You can run...
拉蒙  怎么回事
Ramon, what's happening?
我也不知道  好吗
You know, I don't know, okay?
我什么都看不见  也不知道怎么了
I can't see anything. I don't know what's wrong.
或许我失去超能力了
Maybe I lost my powers.
我都没失去超能力
I didn't lose my powers.
你咋会失去超能力呢
Why would you lose your powers?
好吧  波长触发器没有反应
Oh, here we go, the wavelength trigger's not responding,
那只能是因为
but that only happens if--
频率失调
The frequency is imbalanced.
什么
What?
我的地球的频率和你们的不一样
Our Earth vibrates at a different frequency than yours.
哈里  没了那频率
Harry, without that frequency...
那就麻烦了
We're up a creek.
最近一次袭击是极速精心策划的
The latest attack was orchestrated by Zoom,
极速威胁依然存在
史纳特市长延长宵禁
我们知道中城市民很害怕
and we understand that citizens of Central City are scared,
但我可以向大家保证中城警局
but I can assure you the CCPD
-一直在努力... -那是我
- has been working diligently... - That's me.
-是啊  -在韦斯特警探的领导下
- Yeah, it is. - Under the leadership of Detective West.
我们会阻止极速  我们保证
We will stop Zoom. That's a promise.
"韦斯特警探的领导下"
"The leadership of detective West."
所以乔在这里也是警察
So Joe's still a cop here.
是啊  更重要的是  我还是个鉴证员
Yeah, but more importantly, I'm still a CSI.
我有办法了
I have a plan.
出什么事了
What just happened?
二重身
Doppelganger.
等等  等等  我怎么到这里了
Wait, wait, wait, wait, how did I get here?
什么  你  你是谁
What--who are--who are you?
你怎么和我长得一样
How do you look like me?
艾伦  你在干什么
Allen, what are you doing?
哈里森·威尔斯
Harrison Wells.
传说中的哈里森·威尔斯
The Harrison Wells.
天呐  这是尖端科研实验室吗
Oh, my god, am I in S.T.A.R. labs?
好了  我不知道这是什么情况
Okay, I have no idea what is going on here,
可我一直很想见你
but I've always wanted to meet you.
你写的关于弦唯象学的论文
Your thesis on string phenomenology
在我看来是革命性的理论
was revolutionary to me.
-天呐  -我把那杂志
- Oh, man. - I had the magazine
过塑了  以便收藏
laminated so I could keep it.
-我只是想学习... -受不了这人了
- I-I-I just want to emulate... - This guy's incredible.
我还因此获奖了呢  就在那边  看
I won an award for it, right over there, you see?
太美...
Oh, it's beaut--
你做了什么
Wh--wh--what did you do?
你在干什么啊
What's wrong with you?
你这是变坏了吗
Have you turned into an evil you?
冷静点  只是把他弄晕了
Relax. Just knocked him out.
那你干嘛把他抓过来
Oh, well, why'd you even bring him over here?
那他就可以冒充他了
So he could become him.
你们俩在这边修修护目镜
While you guys work on the goggles,
我冒充他去中城警局  看能否
I will go to CCPD as him and see if I can figure out
拿到他们对极速之前的踪迹掌握的信息
what information they have on Zoom's previous sightings.
根据那些踪迹就可以找到极速的藏身地
We can use those sightings to triangulate Zoom's hideout.
好  计划不错
Good. That's a good plan.
记住杰伊说的  好吗
Just remember what Jay said, okay?
这里的事都有点奇怪
Things here are all sorts of trippy.
听着  没事的
Look, it'll be fine.
我能应付
I can handle it.
很简单
It'll be easy.
自由公正的社会
这太疯狂了
Yo, this is crazy.
自由公正的社会
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off me.
队长
Captain?
听着  我什么都不知道
Look, I don't know nothin',
所以我无可奉告
So I ain't sayin' nothing'.
好
Okay.
死亡射手  什么...
Deadshot, wh--
那可不好笑  艾伦
That's not funny, Allen.
我讨厌这称呼
I hate that nickname.
好  听着  我知道我不是
Okay, look, I know I'm not--
不是局里枪法最好的  可是
I'm not the best shot in the department, but--
不是最好
Not the best?
罗通  你可是全局
Lawton, you are the worst
枪法最烂的好吧
shot in the entire department.
不如你在这里给辛格登记
Hey, why don't you book Singh here,
我一会儿就回来
and I'll be in there in a moment?
都听你的  搭档
Whatever you say, partner.
走吧
Come on.
顺便说一句
Oh, and just for the record,
上个月我的枪法水平等级
my marksmanship proficiency ratings
提高了两个点呢
went up by two points last month.
知道不
All right?
两个点
Two points.
爱瑞丝
Iris.
你是韦斯特警探
You're Detective West.
独一无二  不可替代
The one, the only.
对
Yeah.
你有空吗  犯罪现场鉴证员艾伦
Can I see you for a second, CSI Allen?
-好  -好
- Yeah. - Yeah.
你在干什么啊
Um, what are you doing?
干嘛啊
What?
我认为夫妻之间在
I think a little office PDA
办公室秀点恩爱没什么啊
between husband and wife is okay.
夫妻之间
Husband and wife?
对啊  宣誓和交换戒指之后
Yeah, that's what happens when you do the vows,
我们就是夫妻了啊
exchange the rings.
你的戒指呢
Where is your ring?
别人应该知道
People should know
你已经有主了
that you are a taken man.
-好奇怪  -那是什么
- That's so weird. - What's that?
超能力者警报程序
My meta-human alert app.
这上面显示你是个超能力者
It thinks that you're a meta-human.
那还真是奇怪
That is so weird.
是啊  肯定是坏了
Yeah, it must be on the fritz.
走吧
Let's go.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
回家
Home.
走吧
Come on.
你们是怎么想的
Where do you people get off
敢打劫中城皇家银行
robbing Central City's Royal Bank?
这城市属于极速
This town belongs to Zoom,
和我们这些他认为有能力执行他意愿的人
and those of us he deems worthy enough to enforce his will.
给你
Here.
拿走吧
Take it.
一千万个感谢
Thanks a million.
或者应该说是两千万
Or should I say two?
不要
No.
等等  求你
Wait, please.
别伤害我
Don't hurt me.
伤害你
Hurt you?
我只是想给你个吻
I just want to give you a kiss.
不是跟你说了要注意身后吗
Now what did I tell you about watching that behind?
我还以为那是你的活儿
I thought that was your job.
真不错  我唯一可以亲的人
Good thing the only man I can kiss
恰好是唯一想亲的
is the only one I want to.
刚收到消息  有穿越者过来了
Just got word some breachers came through.
我最喜欢
Ooh, you know my favorite thing
杀另一个地球来的人了
is to kill people from other earths.
今天你走运了
Today's your lucky day.
好棒
This is nice.
我们的家
Our home.
可能是我忘了吧
I mean, I forgot, I guess.
你怎么了
What is wrong with you?
你今天怪怪的
You've been acting weird all day.
我可能是有点不在状态
I'm just not myself, I guess.
你妈妈来过电话
Your mom called.
爸爸
和妈妈
艾迪
布鲁斯
哈尔
戴安娜
这里是艾伦家
Allen residence.
您好
Hello?
-喂  -妈妈
- Uh, hello? - Mom.
天啊  怎么过了这么久才回电话
Wow, you certainly took your time calling back.
是啊  我  我很抱歉
Yeah, um, I'm-- I'm sorry about that.
谢谢你给的
Thank you so much
去亚特兰蒂斯过周年纪念日的票
for the anniversary tickets to Atlantis.
我和你爸爸一直想去来着
Your dad and I have always wanted to go.
你们高兴我就开心了
Um, I'm--I'm really glad you liked them.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你听起来怪怪的
You sound kind of strange.
我没事
I'm fine.
我  我...
I'm--I'm--
我懂
Hey, I know.
要不把机票留给你和爱瑞丝吧
Maybe I should give the plane tickets to you and Iris.
一次浪漫的旅行
Nice little romantic getaway.
借此机会还可以着手要孩子的事
You two could get started on giving me a grandchild.
不  我想让你们去
No, I want you to use them.
听到你高兴...
I'm really glad to...
我真的很开心  妈妈
hear you happy, mom.
我爱你  巴里
Aw, I love you, Barry.
我也爱你
I love you too.
好了  宝贝  再见
Okay, bye-bye, honey.
亲爱的  怎么了
Baby, what's wrong?
没什么
Uh, nothing.
就是...
It was, uh...
跟我妈妈聊得很开心
Um, it was just good to talk to my mom.
我们得做好准备了  是不是
We should get ready, yeah?
-是的  -好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
我不知道  哪里都找不到他
I don't know. I can't find him anywhere.
他最好快点出现
Yeah, well, he better show up soon
都离开好几个小时了
because he's been gone for hours.
再过这么几个小时
And we only have so many of those left
极速就要来索取速度了
before Zoom needs the speed.
原来你说的是巴里
You're talking about Barry.
-是啊  -好吧
- Yeah. - Yeah.
别担心他  他没事的
Don't worry about him. He'll be fine.
不然你以为我说的是谁
Who'd you think I was talking about?
我还以为你说的是我
I thought you were talking about me.
-你  -是啊
- You? - Yeah
因为我们找到了巴里的二重身
'cause we found Barry's double,
我的二重身在哪儿
so where the hell am I?
我一直幻想着
You know, I always thought
在另一个世界里  我会是
in another life I was, like,
我不知道  可能是个非常
I don't know, like a really
富有  著名的发明家
wealthy, famous inventor,
跟地球二的埃隆·马斯克差不多的那种
You know, sort of like the earth-2 Elon Musk.
当然了  没那么苦瓜脸
Only with less RBF, obviously.
给你点建议
Here's some advice for you.
你能不能在寻找极速上多花点时间
How about spending more time looking for Zoom
而不是浪费在琢磨并不是你的那个人
and less time worrying about what someone who is not you
和他们过着什么样的生活上
is doing with their life?
吉特巴舞[爵士舞曲]
*有些事*
*Some things that happened*
*发生过一次*
*For the first time*
*似乎还会*
*Seem to be happening*
*重现*
*Again*
*因此  仿佛你我*
*And so it seems that we have*
*曾经相遇*
*Met before*
*曾一同欢笑*
*And laughed before*
*曾经相爱*
*And loved before*
乔竟然会唱歌
Joe can sing.
他是最棒的
He's the best.
没错
Right.
*谁知道*
*Who knows?*
*是啊  谁知道呢*
*Yeah, who knows*
*哪里又或是何时*
*Where or When?*
宝贝
Hey, baby.
乔  你好
Joe, hey.
叫我约瑟夫  巴塞洛缪
It's Joseph, Bartholomew.
老爸  友善点
Pop, be nice.
你也是  宝贝
You too, babe.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
好
Yeah.
所以你是歌手
So you're a singer.
你依然是个傻子
So you're still an idiot.
你生我的气了吗
Are you upset with me?
还是你就是不太喜欢我
Or you just-- you just don't like me?
你脑子出问题了吗
Have you lost your mind?
中城现在都要完蛋了
Central city's going to hell
就因为这个疯子极速
in a handbasket because this lunatic Zoom
在到处杀人
is running around killing folks,
而你让我女儿站到了最前线
and you got my daughter on the front lines.
等等  什么  我
Wait--wh--me?
一直都是因为你  巴塞洛缪
It has always been about you, Bartholomew.
你是我见过的最自私的人
You're the most selfish person I've ever met.
我是音乐家  我们都很自私
And I'm a musician, we're all selfish.
你想要去读博士
You wanted to get your Phd
从而能让你的事业更进一步
so you could further your career,
她不得不去做警察
and she had to become a police officer
来给你付学费
to pay your tuition.
我们都知道
We both know
她回去报社工作去才是最安全的
that she'd be safer going back to write at the newspaper.
爸爸  得了  别说了
Oh, dad, please, stop.
我在中城时报只是实习
CCPN was an internship.
我所做的全都是给真正的作家们端咖啡
All I did was get coffee for real writers.
像祖父一样做个警察才是我爱做的
Being a cop like grandpa is what I love.
你教我要坚强  我做到了
You raised me to be tough, and I am.
一切都很好
Everything's fine,
我们来这里是消遣开心的  对吧
and we're here to have fun, right?
没错
Right.
一切都好极了
Everything's great.
怎么样了
How's it going?
很慢  这可不是一个好的词
Uh, slow, which is not a good adjective
来形容神速炮
when it comes to a speed cannon.
好吧  我们又有了一个问题
Well, we got another problem.
为什么我们总是有另一个问题
Why do we always have to have another problem?
你得来看看
You've got to see this.
快去叫闪电侠
Somebody call the Flash.
超能力者袭击
他叫亚当·福尔斯
His name is Adam Fells,
但他自称地卜师
but he calls himself Geomancer.
这个超能力者是从缺口来的吗
So this meta-human is a breacher?
不是  福尔斯在我的地球上已经死了
No, Fells died on my earth.
这个肯定是地球一那个的二重身
This must be his Earth-1 doppelganger.
至少现在我们知道他的名字了
Well, at least now, we know his name.
也许能更容易追踪到他
Might be a little easier to track him down.
但是现在巴里不在了
Yeah, but with Barry gone,
就算我们找到他  我们要怎么阻止他呢
how are we gonna stop him even if we do find him?
杰伊  你可以再注射那个东西
Well, Jay, you could shoot yourself up with that stuff.
叫什么来着  终极速度
What was it? Velocity--
-终极速度-6 -我不能用终极速度-6
- Velocity-6. - I cannot take V-6.
但是那能让你重新恢复速度
But it gave you your speed back long enough to get that
从威尔斯体内取出子弹  救他的命
bullet out of Wells, saved his life.
乔  不要让我再用终极速度-6了
Joe, don't ask me to take Velocity-6 again.
杰伊  我不是要告诉你应该怎么做
Look, Jay, I'm not trying to tell you what to do,
但是巴里在保护你的世界
but Barry is protecting your world,
而我们的世界现在需要闪电侠
and our world needs a Flash right about now.
杰伊
Jay.
凯特琳  我喜欢你现在看我的方式
Caitlin, I like the way you look at me
那种热情和骄傲  而我
with warmth and pride, and I'm not--
我不值得那些
I'm not worthy of those.
不  你值得
Yes, you are.
不  我做了很糟糕的事情  凯特琳
No, I did a terrible thing, Caitlin.
当我世界的粒子加速器爆炸后
When my world's particle accelerator went off,
我变成了极速者
I became a speedster.
我变成了世上速度最快的人
I became the fastest man alive,
只是那对我仍是不够
only--only it wasn't enough for me.
我还不够快
I wasn't-- I wasn't fast enough.
所以我想我能利用我的科学背景
So I figured with my scientific background,
来增加我的速度
I could increase my powers,
并且我做到了
and...I did.
所以你之前使用过终极速度-6
So you've taken Velocity-6 before?
是的
Yes.
但是却出现了预料外的副作用
But there were some unforeseen side effects.
这就是我不想巴里使用它
This is why you didn't want Barry to take it
甚至知道它的存在
or even know about it.
极速没有偷走你的速度
Zoom never stole your speed.
这个才是让你虚弱的原因
This is what's making you sick.
终极速度-6正在杀死你
Velocity-6 is killing you.
我说这些东西很危险不是在骗你
I wasn't lying when I said that stuff was dangerous.
我犯了太多错误
I've made so many mistakes.
你现在已经拥有了
You have something now
你之前从没有的东西
that you've never had before.
我
Me.
我会想出解决办法的
And I'm gonna figure this out.
*我幽默的情人*
*My funny valentine*
*甜美风趣的情人*
*Sweet comic valentine*
我们能多谈谈
So can we talk more about
为什么约瑟夫不喜欢我吗
why Joseph doesn't like me?
有什么好谈的
What's there to talk about?
我是说  你也忍受不了他
I mean, you can't stand him either.
好吧
Right.
但就算你们互相讨厌对方
Look, I can love you both
我还是很爱你们俩
even if you don't love each other.
超能力者提醒软件
The meta-human warning app.
继续唱  老头子
Don't stop singing, old man.
那是我们的歌
That's our song.
那么  你们这些花花公子中有谁
So which one of you lounge lizards
是来错宇宙了呢
is in the wrong universe?
请举手吧
Show of hands.
别害羞
Don't be shy.
别别别
No, no, no.
帅哥
Hey, handsome.
你是不是有话要跟我说
You got something you want to tell me?
没有
No.
没有吗
No?
宝贝  没人要跟我说话
Baby, no one's talking to me.
如果我让他们尖叫呢
What if I make 'em scream?
中城警局
CCPD!
-大家都离开这里  -大家快走
- Everyone get out of here. - All right, go, go.
你们俩都被逮捕了
You are both under arrest.
女士优先
Ladies first.
凯特琳
Caitlin.
我很久没听到这个名字了
I haven't heard that name in a long time.
但那是你的名字  不是吗
But that is your name, isn't it?
你的真名
Your real name?
听我说
Please, look...
我了解你
I know you.
别这么做
Don't do this.
如果你真的了解我
If you knew me at all,
你应该知道我讨厌凯特琳这个名字
you would know that I hate the name Caitlin.
我是冰霜杀手
I'm Killer Frost.
快走  快走
Go, all right. Go, go!
爱瑞丝  小心
Iris, look out!
爸爸
Dad!
天呐
Oh, my God.
你好啊  穿越者
Well, hello, breacher.
他是个极速者  宝贝
He's a speedster, babe.
我在颤抖
Oh, I'm shivering.
我早就想干掉闪电侠了
I've been dying to kill the Flash.
我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you.
相信我  你伤不到我
Trust me, you won't.
干掉他
Kill him.
来吧
Come on.
天啊  这真让我感到狂热
God, this is making me so hot.
这事没完  穿越者
This ain't over, breacher.
巴里
Barry!
天呐
Oh, my God.
巴里
Barry?
冰霜杀手和死亡风暴
Killer Frost and Deathstorm.
-你知道他们吗  -更重要的是
- You know them? - More importantly,
他们现在知道你的存在  知道你来了
they know you now; they know that you're here.
凯特琳和罗尼的二重身都是坏蛋吗
So Caitlin and Ronnie's doppelgangers are evil?
但是这些名字酷毙了
Those are some dope names, though.
这本该是讲精准的任务  艾伦
This was supposed to be a surgical mission, Allen.
找到极速的巢穴  救出杰西
Find Zoom's lair. Rescue Jesse.
办完回来  别插手其他的事
Get in, get out, not get involved.
我已经插手了  好吗
All right, well, look, I am involved, okay?
乔现在医院里  他们差点杀死他
Joe's in the hospital. They nearly killed him.
不  他没有
No, he isn't.
乔·韦斯特  你认识的乔·韦斯特
Joe West, your Joe West,
在你的地球上安然无恙地活着
is alive and safe on your earth,
凯特琳和爱瑞丝也是
so is Caitlin, so is Iris.
这些人  巴里  他们只是倒影
These people, Barry, they're mirror reflections.
就你的生活而言  他们不存在
As far as your life is concerned, they don't exist.
冰霜杀手和死亡风暴知道你来了
Killer Frost, Deathstorm, they know that you're here.
极速很快也会知道  然后我女儿就会死
Then it's not long before Zoom does too, and then
这全是你一手照成的
my daughter's dead, and that's on you.
杰西还有时间
Jesse still has time, okay?
爱瑞丝和乔现在需要我
Iris and Joe need me now.
-我得回去救他们  -她不是爱瑞丝
- I have to get back to them! - She is not Iris!
她就是爱瑞丝
She is Iris!
对我来说她是
Okay, she is to me!
不管我身处在哪一个地球  他们都是我的家人
No matter what universe I'm in, they are my family!
我想到这个时候  你应该明白家人的重要性
I would think by now you should get how important family is.
我要去  威尔斯
I'm going, Wells.
我必须去
I have to.
找到极速
Find Zoom.
亚当·福尔斯
我通过广播干扰找到了亚当·福尔斯
I ran Adam Fells through BCI.
在成为超能力者前  他也不是什么模范公民
Not exactly a model citizen before he was a meta-human.
曾犯过多起抢劫和攻击人身罪
Multiple counts of robbery and assault.
如果他认为可以利用我的城市
Well, if he thinks he's gonna use my city
和闪电侠来场铁笼死亡赛的话
for a steel cage death match with the Flash,
那他就有的受了
he's got another thing coming.
你怎么来了
Hey, what are you doing here?
等等  我们本来约好要见面吗
Wait, were we supposed to meet up or something?
不是  我正好在附近
No, I was-- I was just nearby.
大家没事吧
Everybody okay?
发现了福尔斯
Fells has been spotted.
帕斯科区第四街
Pasko and Fourth.
出发
Go.
我得走了  孩子
I got to go, son.
乔
Joe--
爸爸  你没事吧
Dad, are you okay?
该死的超能力者
Damn meta-humans.
我最最讨厌的地方
Only thing I hate more...
就是医院
is hospitals.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
我担心你
Just worried about you.
这可是头一回
There's a first.
宝贝
Baby.
你有发现
You ever notice every time
每次我唱歌之前
just before I do a number,
都会闭眼一小下  然后深呼吸吗
I close my eyes for a hot second and I take a deep breath?
你知道我那是在干嘛吗
You ever wonder what I was doing?
在记歌词吗
Trying to remember the lyrics?
我每次唱歌之前
I say a little mantra to myself
会默念一次
every time before I sing.
"为我的宝贝
"This one is for Iris.
爱瑞丝而唱"
My baby girl."
每首歌都是为你而唱的  宝贝
Every song's for you, baby.
每一句歌词
Every single one.
爸爸  别说了  好吗
Dad, don't talk like this, okay?
巴...巴里
Wh--B--Barry.
照顾她
You take care of her.
爸爸
Dad?
爸爸  爸爸  护士
Dad? Dad? Nurse!
医生  护士
Doctor! Nurse!
爸爸
Dad!
爱瑞丝
Iris.
不要离开我
No, no, no!
不要  不要
No! No!
没事的
It's okay.
妈的
Oh, damn it.
你不用这么做  罗通
You don't have to do this, Lawton.
我们是搭档啊
We're partners, right?
你一直挺我
You've always had my back,
我也挺你
and I've got yours.
爱瑞丝
Oh, Iris.
-我认识你吗  -她认识我吗
- Do I know you? - Does she know me?
这是我的好友西斯科·拉蒙
Uh, this is my good friend, Cisco Ramon.
-好友  -是的
- Good friend? - Yeah.
西斯科在尖端科研实验室工作
Cisco works at S.T.A.R. Labs,
他造了个他认为可以用来
and he has built a weapon that he believes we can use
对付冰霜杀手超能力的武器
to neutralize, um, Killer Frost's powers.
很好  谢谢
Great, thanks.
交给我吧
I'll take it.
还是我来拿着好了
Please, I should really take this.
好吧
All right.
我的线人给我提供了
One of my snitches gave me a lead
冰霜杀手和死亡风暴的位置
on Killer Frost and Deathstorm's location.
我们要把他们抓回来
We're gonna bring them in.
好  我跟你一起去  爱瑞丝
Okay, um, I'm coming with you, Iris.
不行  巴里  我刚失去了父亲
No. Barry, I just lost my father.
我不能再失去丈夫
I cannot lose my husband too.
好吧  只有西斯科知道
All right, well, Cisco's the only one that knows
怎么操作这个装置  你必须带上他
how to operate the device, so you have to take him.
我不能让市民陷入危险
I can't put a civilian in harm's way.
我见过各种大场面
Look, I've seen fire, and I've seen rain.
我会照顾好自己  韦斯特-艾伦夫人
I can handle myself, okay, Mrs. West-Allen.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
罗通  行动吧
Lawton, let's move.
好的...
Yeah, uh--
我们一定要找到杰西
We need to work on finding Jesse.
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure this is what you want to be doing?
确定
I am, all right?
现在  我们先帮助爱瑞丝
Right now, we have to help Iris.
大家都要毫发无损地回来
Just make sure no one else gets hurt.
中城警察  投降吧  福尔斯
CCPD! It's over, Fells!
请勿见怪  蓝衣人儿
No offense to you boys in blue,
我想见的是红衣人
but I'm waiting on the man in red.
你最好希望闪电侠不会出现
You better hope The Flash doesn't show up,
否则你就玩完了
or you're finished.
挺有意思
See, that's funny.
我觉得他不会出现
I don't think he will show.
我已经翻天覆地好几天了
I've been causing tremors for days
他都没有出现
and no sign of him.
他应该不在这里
I think he's gone.
拳击赛里经常这么说
What is it they say in boxing?
看谁雄霸天下
Let's get ready to rumble.
怎么...
What the-- -
我听说你在找闪电侠
I heard you were looking for The Flash.
看来终极速度-7起作用了
Looks like the velocity-7 is working.
抓住他吧
Now, go get him.
新招数
That's a new one.
你只有这点能耐吗
Is that all you have?
你不想知道我有多少能耐
You don't ever want to see all I have.
终极速度-7快耗尽了
The velocity-7's wearing off.
你知道八级地震
You've heard what an eight on the Richter scale
有多大的威力吗
can do to a city.
想想你的头骨会有什么下场
Imagine what it's gonna do to your skull.
你受伤了吗
You hurt?
我的尊严
My pride
还有我的身体
and my body.
尊严和身体
Pride and my body.
你确定就是这里吗
You really sure this is the place?
也许你该待在车里  罗通
Maybe you should stay in the car, Lawton.
快点  先生们
Look alive, gents.
也许你收错风了
Hey, maybe--maybe your snitch was wrong.
也许他们根本不在这里
I mean, maybe they're not even here.
不  他们就在这里
No, they're here.
你们没敲门
You didn't knock.
真没礼貌
How rude.
把枪放下
Drop 'em.
罗尼
Ronnie.
马丁·斯泰因跟你在一起吗
Is Martin Stein in there?
我很久没放他出来了
Oh, I haven't let him out in years.
他没什么机会说话
Doesn't talk much anymore.
你杀了我父亲  你个贱婊子
You killed my father, you evil bitch.
他不该与穿越者为伍
He shouldn't have palled around with a breacher.
这是极速最不允许的事
That's a big no-no as far as Zoom's concerned.
我不敢相信你们为极速办事
I can't believe you two work for Zoom.
不  他们为我办事
No, they work for me.
我为极速办事
I work for Zoom.
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
挺有意思
Well, that's funny.
我本来也要问你这个问题
I was just gonna ask you the same thing.
-二重... -身
- Doppel... - Ganger.
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
你们两个有什么关系
Are you two related to each other?
我知道还有一个我在这里
Oh, I knew there was another me here.
西斯科  在你进入缺口
And I knew you were coming, Cisco,
踏足这个世界之前  我就知道你会过来
even before you entered the breach and set foot on this world.
我们之间有联系
See, we're all connected...
弗朗西斯科
Francisco.
我叫震波
My name is Vibe.
回波
Reverb.
这个名字取得比上不足
Actually not the worst name you could've come up with,
比下有余
but not the best.
我一直在观察你  震波
I've been watching you, Vibe,
我只能说我非常失望
and I have to say I am extremely disappointed.
我知道这种感觉
Yeah, I know the feeling.
我不知道哪个比较糟
I'm not sure what's worse,
你是极速的党羽
the fact that you're part of Zoom's gang,
还是你头上
or that weird samurai situation
顶着个武士头
you got going on on the top of your head there.
你听着
Listen to this.
如果极速
What if Zoom
不再主导这出戏了呢
wasn't running the show anymore?
你在说什么
What do you mean?
你不知道自己有多强大
You don't even know how powerful you are.
你一直把强大的力量浪费在这些小把戏上
All you use your powers for are these cheap parlor tricks
如果你...你会成为神
when you... you could be a god.
我们都会成为神
We could be gods.
我可不想当什么黑武士
Are you Cloud City vadering me right now?
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
把他们交给极速吧
Let's turn them over to Zoom.
再这么跟我说话
Speak to me like that again,
我会毫不费劲地
and I will shatter your entire nervous system
把你废了
without breaking a sweat.
那么  震波
So, Vibe...
你要管理中城吗
do you want to run Central City?
你说呢
What do you say?
我说
I say...
闪电侠  救我们
Flash, save us!
你没被伤到吧
Hey, that didn't hurt you, did it?
-没有  怎么会伤到我  -我不知道
- No. Why would it? - I don't know.
你到底是谁
And who the hell are you?
警探  赶紧离开这里吧
Look, detective, just get out of here, all right?
不  必须带上他们
No, not without them.
待在这里
Stay here!
第二回合
Round two.
镜子影像  我告诉过你了
Look, mirror-mirror, I already told you
我不要跟你黑化
I'm not going to the dark side with you.
你的手活太渣了
You're a rotten shot.
我就不渣
I'm not.
难道我也有这种能耐
Are you telling me I can do that?
我可以展现给你看
I can show you.
不
No!
住手  你们都住手
Stop, both of you!
极速要活捉他
Zoom wanted him alive.
你知道不听极速的指示有什么下场
You know what Zoom will do if you don't obey him.
不
No!
什么
That.
我告诉过你遇到极速者时
What did I say you should do
该怎么做吗
if you encountered a speedster?
不能伤害他
Leave him unharmed.
你觉得这样不算伤害吗
Does this look unharmed to you?
我很高兴
I'm happy to see
至少还有你知道点分寸
at least one of you knows their place.
巴里
Barry!
不
No.
抱歉
Sorry.
我是不是忘了告诉你可能会疼
Did I forget to say this might sting?
我不是第一次受伤了
It's not my first road rash.
记得我是极速者吗
I'm a speedster, remember?
今天你让大家记住了
You made sure no one will forget that today.
多亏你
Thanks to you.
终极速度-7挺好用的
The velocity-7 held up pretty well.
准备开发终极速度-8
Moving on to velocity-8.
我保证我会开发出来的
I'm gonna figure it out, I swear.
我需要你想办法稳定缺口
I just need you to figure out how to re-stabilize the breach.
巴里  西斯科和威尔斯还有24小时
Barry, Cisco, and Wells still have 24 hours to go.
我们要善用这一天的时间
So we have one day,
否则他们永远回不来了
or they could be stuck there forever.
杰西  杰西
Jesse. Jesse!
我跟你爸爸一起来了
Hey. I'm here with your dad!
我们会救你出去  知道吗
We're gonna get you out of here, all right?
我保证
I promise.
对你无法做到的事
It's not wise
做出保证  并不明智  闪电侠
to make promises you can't keep, Flash.
看看周围
Look around.
这是...
This...
你最后
is the last place
看见的地方
you'll ever see.